for the majority of people on YouTube
quantitative Finance isn't a
particularly sexy topic and therefore
it's not a huge Channel that I have
however for those who are interested and
those who really enjoy the topic of
quantitative finance and mathematical
Finance I try and put the best content
that I possibly can out but on my
Twitter account it's a little bit
different so if we see here in my
Twitter account I started off trying to
post um irregularly sporadically and I
wasn't getting much traction so instead
I've decided to use the open API chat
GPT to come up with better suggestions
for what content I can put on Twitter I
then use the API to take these
suggestions generate content engaging
content that then I can post regularly
using the Twitter API so in this video
we're going to be going through that
entire process and how you can actually
do some prompt engineering use the
Jupiter notebooks that I have and all
the code I've put available on my GitHub
repository and the link is in the
description so if you want to automate
your Twitter feed with whatever type of
content that you're putting out doesn't
need to be quantitative Finance you can
use my template in jupyter Notebook do
your own prompt engineering use the
templates and change it of course for
your topic uh that's unrelated to
quantitative Finance so the GitHub
repository just for a bit of an overview
of what this project is I have this
running on a Raspberry Pi cluster but
you could have it running on any server
that you want essentially all I'm doing
is I'm using open API chat GPT to
generate the Twitter post given a list
of quantitative python ideas now how did
I come up with these ideas well I simply
asked chat GPT so I told chat BT that I
run a YouTube channel called Quant piy
where I talk about quantitative Finance
on this channel I make tutorials where I
break down complicated mathematics in
finance and make it easy to digest I
made a spelling error python tutorials
the uh tutorials are practical and
mostly under uh 20 minutes in length so
the respon response was really nothing
answer there so I obviously didn't
prompt chat BT very well but it asked
how can I assist can you please help me
further my channel and then provide me
some content ideas and see here it's
given me a list of content ideas um for
different aspects of my channel in
quantitative Finance so that's a good
start at this point here I wanted to
remind it of a previous conversation
that I had where it had given me a
number of other topics of conversations
General Topics in quantitative fun
Finance so I said previously you would
advised me to write short content on
engaging topics in quantitative finance
and I gave it what it what it put out to
me with a list of topics to cover now I
said could you please construct a list
of 100 video ideas and create a table
structure um with number topic and title
as the three column headers so it's gone
ahead and it's done this and I did ask
for some influence over um some popular
sites in quantitative Finance so here
Quant stack exchange it's gone ahead and
then it's given me a table with number
topic title so here uh I had to prompt
it again because it didn't um print out
51 to 100 so I said please continue
writing ideas 51 to 100 and it's given
me in this table format here but I need
something that I can put to a text file
so then I can actually use Python to
process it so I said can you please
convert the table format to text table
with a divider of um this divisor here
so no problem of course here's a list
with the divider I copy the code and I
put it down in a text file so the second
step to this is using open API API and
the first thing you're going to need to
do is you're going to need an API key so
when you go to their website then you
need to click try chat BT or log in so
what that does is that there's actually
two platforms most people have been
interacting with the Jack GPT as we've
just been doing um in the chat atbot
format whereas there is this nice uh API
so I'm going to click on the API section
I've already got an account you can sign
in here and then if I click on personal
and I look at um view API Keys you're
going to set up your own API Keys here
so you'd come into the user section and
obviously you're going to be rate
limited if you've only got a free
account but you would create a new set
of keys um you would give it a name and
then you would get an open AI API key so
that's step number one the second step
is you're going to need Twitter account
details so you're going to need to go
Link in the description of the Twitter
developer account you're going to need
to give it 250 word description on why
you need this account and what you'll be
doing again I actually just used chat B
gbt I could not think of uh a
description for 250 words to then
justify why I needed this development
account so I said look I need this
account just because I want to automate
my Twitter account chat BBT can you
please come up with 250 word description
enter um got into my Twitter account
then essentially what you need to do you
need to create an app I can only have
one free environment one free app under
my account and it is rate limited again
and I can only post up to 1,500 tweets
per month under that I then have my
specific um app details and my key keys
and
tokens so here I've got consumer Keys
API key and secret I won't reveal them
here but then you also have
authentication tokens so Bearer token
and then access token and secret token
so you will need all five of these so
just explaining a little bit about what
this project is I have this project set
up on a Raspberry Pi but it could be any
server so it utilizes open API GPT
and we're going to generate those
Twitter ideas we're going to take those
lists that we've just come up with we're
going to then process that list we're
going to actually generate the content
and then when we're ready we're going to
post intermittently using the tweey API
and we're going to use the AP scheduler
module in Python to actually deliver
this every 12 hours now the cool thing
here is we're actually going to be
creating a service that runs on a server
um here I've got a Linux server where we
can actually control our bot we can
start we can stop we can um understand
what the status of our Twitter bod is
and it makes it so much easier to handle
in the command line so let's talk about
um the actual content generation and how
we take our list of ideas and process
them so one of the first things that
we're going to do we're going to take a
look at the prompt engineering uh
Jupiter notebook and this is thanks to
Lang Chang promp in template and we've
adapted this from um this GitHub
repository here but essentially I don't
want to have to um develop my prompting
method every time I want to be able to
call this as a processing function in
Python so let's understand what the L
Chang library is and how we can do some
prompt engineering to get the correct
response and the Twitter format that we
need so here I'm importing my
dependencies and from Lang Chang um pip
install langang if you don't have it
we're going to be taking the chat open
API um module and from the Lang chen.
prompts we're going to be taking the
chat prompt template the system message
prompt template the AI message prompt
template and the human message prompt
template so the only API key I have here
is just the API key for open API and you
could of course put it here but I have
it to to aend file which is a little bit
safer I then also have the directory
variables which just map back to my raw
data file so let's take a look at some
of the prompt engineering how I'm
actually um interacting with chat GPT
the first thing I need to do I need to
use the Lang Chang um chat open API uh
module and set up the large language
model we're going to initialize our
large language model with a temperature
the learning rate of. 3 um you can you
can try different variations to try and
get the best out of it and try and
encourage creativity we've got we're
sending in our open API API key and
we're also choosing the model name now
there are many models to choose from and
if we look back at our developer API
account so what you can see is that
there are many different models that we
can use and all the documentation on
what they do and what they're best at is
specific and specified within the
documentation here on their website but
here um we're giving it's it's said that
the best recommendation is the turbo 3.5
turbo account for the free account um
and this is the latest one so that's
what I'm going to be using here's my
main function where I'm going to be
generating a response so let's set the
context
the variables that I have coming in is
my large language model that I've just
set up I want to give it a Quant topic
from my big list and I want to give it a
Quant title so let's understand what
we're trying to do we're going to get
out a tupal of a long response and a
short response from chat be gbt and I'll
explain about why we're giving getting
two responses back in a second the first
thing we need to understand is the
system template and this is the template
that we're giving open AI to give
context about what it has to do and who
it has to be while responding to the
human the human input messages so I'm
telling the system open API that you are
an incredibly wise and smart
quantitative analyst that lives and
breathes the world of quantitative
Finance your goal is to write short form
content for Twitter given a topic in the
area of quantitative finance and a title
from the user so the response tone I
want the tone to to be um have an active
voice and be opinionated your tone
should be serious with a hit hint of wit
and sarcasm and this has been adapted
from that GitHub repository like we have
in the link above we want to be
extremely clear and concise with the
format respond with phrases no longer
than two sentences and do not respond
with Emojis so we also want the response
content to include examples of where
this is used in quantitative Finance
space and if you can't answer say sorry
I'll have to ask the Quant Finance Gods
so the Quant uh the response template I
can actually specify and here's where
the prompt engineering really comes down
to I want a specific format that I can
always use for my Twitter um feed so the
response format I again asked chat be
GPT what it recommended and it said for
engaging article I should have a hook an
intro an explanation an application of
where it's used a closing statement a
call to action and then an engagement uh
section so no problem I use that
template and I've given it here in the
system instruction so I want to captive
one liner a brief introduction to the
topic I want to simplify the core idea
notes real world relevance reflective
oneliner short engagement call and a
quick question so this is my response
template that I want every tweet to
follow now how do I adapt that um as a
system message well I use the system
message prompt template and I say from
template and I pass that big string then
what I need to do I need to provide the
human template and the only two things
the human's going to be providing again
is the topic and the title and I do
often add that keep the total response
under 200 words total so I'm just really
telling chat gbt that it needs to be
concise because for Twitter we've only
got 280 characters um per post so that's
important so here I'm using the human
message prompt template from temp
template exactly the same as again but
you'll you'll see here that I have these
um curly brackets which indicate
variables and I can use the prompt
template from prompt template structure
to pass in the input variables that I'm
going to pass as the human messaging
interface so the way that I can then
construct that chat prompt template with
both the system
uh message prompt and then the human
message prompt is by using the chat
prompt template and we're going to use
the dot uh from messages and we're going
to combine just in a list format those
two prompt messages in the correct order
so system message first and then the
human message prompt now obviously we
haven't passed in the correct topic and
title yet but in my variable name I have
that I am passing the Quant topic and
the Quant title
so I'm going to say to get a final
completed chat my final prompt I'm going
to use this chat prompt template that
I've created and I need to pass in these
two variables so going to pass in topic
and that's going to be equal to my Quant
topic and then title is going to be
equal to the Quant title variable that
I'm passing in with my overall function
then I'm going to use the two messages
now I actually need to pass this to my
large language model so pass this
template that's been formatted with a
correct qu topic correct Quant title and
then I want to actually get the response
content so the first response is coming
straight from the large language model
with my final prompt in brackets.
content now I tested this multiple times
and what I was getting is a very large
response it's very hard to control the
length of chat gbts um essentially
creativity so what I'm doing is now I'm
going to construct an AI I template to
pass back the response of open AI so I'm
going to tell open AI that it has given
me this first response and the way that
I can do that I can create an AI message
prompt template from Lang Chang so I'm
now creating that template as the first
response and then I'm going to add
another human input and this this
additional human input is just going to
be a prompt reminder that the length was
way too long and that I need it much
shorter so I'm saying this was a good
but way too long please make your
response more concise and much shorter
make phrases no longer than 15 words in
to Total please maintain the existing
template and here is where I'm really
specifying that I need it to be Twitter
length I need it to be less than 280 uh
characters so now I've got that human
message prompt template all I need to do
is then construct my long uh chat prompt
template from messages so again here's
where we combine with a list my system
message now then my human message my
first API uh AI message prompt response
the message that it gave us back and
then the reminder prompt so now we're
going to complete that chat again
formatting it with a correct Quant topic
and Quant title and then again we pass
that whole thing back through um the API
and essentially I'm going to have I want
my first response and my short
response so let's give it an example
here we're going to run through the
generated response First Response and
short response for quantitative topic
and let's see what we get back we're
going to get first response and short
response so I've got the hook I've got
um intro and then I've got application I
have the structure that I need but you
can see it's just returned in one big
text and it's pretty long let's take a
look at the short
response the short response is obviously
much sh shorter excellent so now that I
have these text uh strings how can I
actually process them well the way I'm
going to be um looking for my my
template key features so they the
they're just something that I'm going to
have as my key list and they're
dependent on what I had in this
structure here so I'm going to take hook
I'm going to take intro explanation
application uh closing action and
engagement and I'm going to search for
them knowing that they come in this
string every time so I just provide that
as a key list and I'm going to extract
the tweet and I'm going to save it down
as a dictionary so in Python I have the
template as a dictionary I'm going to
enumerate through my key list and I'm
going to build up this dictionary with
my key list so what does that look like
well essentially at the end of the day I
get when I pass the extract tweet and I
pass the correct key list um with this
function then I get get back my
dictionary with the hook as the key well
with with all the important template
parameters as the key and then my values
are the correct statement so doing that
for the short response as well you can
see much shorter than a long response so
at this point you might be going okay
great so now we've come up with a way to
actually process using prompt
engineering our uh tweets through one
function called generate uncore tweets
that's great now I need to pass the
actual
Quant topics in a systemized fashion how
do we do that well the first thing we
need to do is we need to process our raw
text file so moving back to visual
studio code what did our raw text files
look like well if we take a look at our
raw text files essentially they were in
this format I have um number topic title
I've got these underscores here um so
the first two rows of this is useless
and then I have my number topic title
and I just have that in a format down to
100 and I also did this a second time um
in in context ideas so we've got two
files that look like this and all I want
to do is process them and put them back
in a systemized format so how am I going
to process those files well essentially
I'm just going to open them um with the
file open uh function of the raw text
file and I defined the location before
with the read then I'm going to run
through by enumerating the file read
lines and I'm going to get back the line
number and the line if the line number
is greater than one because remember the
first two rows have the headings and the
underlines then I'm going to start
processing how do I process I'm going to
split on the line devises and then I'm
going to capture those items from this
list the first item is going to be the
Tweet number then I'm going to get the
Tweet top topic and then I'm going to
process the Quant title I need to store
this in a logical way in a dictionary so
I can process it so my dictionary is
Quant tweets so here I've got um the
Tweet number is the uh index and I'm
actually creating a subd dictionary
where then I can Define the topic and
the title for easy reference I'm then
just going to print out a string
representation of what this looks like
so you can understand that I can then
also uh create a quantity tweets text
file whereby I'm going to run through
this dictionary and an organize way and
then save it down in the new format
format that I want for saving these down
is going to be six parts one's going to
be the Tweet number one's going to be
the topic one's going to be the title
then I have three flags which are false
false false at the start and we'll
explain why that is so now I've saved
down my file for Quant tweets into this
text file and I've got all these false
Flags now why did I do that well I'll
show you a completed version of what it
looks like at the end I'm using this is
my database I'm being a bit of a cheap
scape I can't be bothered to set up a
SQL light database or a postgress or
anything like that um I'm just doing it
and saving it down to a text file very
simple very quick easy to do so we're
not storing that much data and it's not
that hard so this is going to be my
database now the flags are going to be
for the first one have you sent it true
or false second one is going to be have
you generated it from open API true or
false and then the third one is less
about a flag and more about storing the
actual Twitter tweet structure so as you
can see in my completed structure I have
I've sent this one true I have generated
it true and then um I have my tweet
structure as a dictionary now for other
ones you can see here I haven't sent it
but I have generated it true and you can
see the dictionary for other structures
you can see it's still false false false
because I haven't done anything with
them speaking about the structure now so
I'm going to have my call opener so I've
got this module set up called Quant
piore feed so the module has a couple of
files the first one that's important is
just going to be the call open API which
we have already been using so that's
what we've just uh the generate tweet
function that we've just come up with in
jupyter
Notebook the second important one is
going to be process tweak so in this
script here in process tweets what we're
going to do is we're going to define
those keywords our key count functions
and we're going to define those extract
tweets and then the generate tweets so
for everything that we did in the
jupyter notebooks this is where we
actually execute it so when I generate a
tweet I want to do some login I want to
generate my response from a specific uh
tweet topic and my and my tweet title I
then want to generate them and I want to
store it down into a dictionary format
and then I want to be able to pass this
uh dictionary format into some kind of
structured data format that's easy to
work with and one smart way to do that
in Python is through data classes so
we're going to have classes that hold my
data structure so here we've got data
classes first I've got um two ANS which
are just flags for the first one so I've
got a Boolean flag a true or false and
then I've also got a tweet type which is
going to be single or threaded so
because I want to Define are we going to
send as a single thread is it under 280
characters or can I send it as a actual
thread whereby I'm sending an initial
message and then I'm replying back to it
so I want to set that as a flag and as a
possible setting for this twitterbot so
now I need a way to actually store my
tweets so as before we had a dictionary
um of our key title so naturally it
makes sense to have the those um
templates those keys as our actual
attributes of this class object so I've
got a hook an intro explanation um
application closing action engagement um
as all strings and I want to be able to
pass through a dictionary so the way
that I can pass through a dictionary and
get back an instance of this class is
through the class method I'm going to
have a from dictionary pass the class
I'm I want to return the class back and
then I want to be able to pass my
Twitter dictionary and all I'm doing is
that I'm um identifying which are the
keys within the dictionary that
correspond to my attribute of this class
instance and I'm creating that class I
then also want to be able to have a
method where I can take an instance of
this class and then send it to a text so
I'm going to use this function when I'm
then going about to send the tweet and I
want to be able to create um a text
version that I can send directly to
Twitter so the track tweet is an object
class for just tracking the status of
individual tweets so here we're going to
have an ID we're going to have a topic
we're going to have a title we're going
to have the sent status the generation
status and then the Tweet so that you'll
notice that again that's the structure
of our text file that we're storing
we're going to have a from string
generate because we want to be able to
read and write back to our text file so
if we want to be able to take a tweet
line in split it on this uh horizontal
devisor and then get back the ID the
topic the title The sent status the Gen
status and the tweet and of course we
had the next line uh symbol which we're
not going to be using so then we want to
convert the status and the generation
status to a true or false enum
representation so all I'm doing is I'm
saying is this uh name true and if it's
true then give it the Boolean do true or
if it's not it'll be false and therefore
give it the Boolean do false and I do
the same thing for uh for sent status as
generation status then I need to
initialize a class without the Tweet
because it doesn't have a tweet to begin
with and it just has false so I
initialize the
class and um you can see that the way
that I've been able to enable that is I
have the field representation for the
Tweet attribute as false so a knit false
and the reason is because when we're
first reading these things in I haven't
generated them then then I just want to
indicate that if I do have the Gen
status as a ball as a Boolean if it is
true then I need to actually add that I
do have the Tweet so I'm going to say
tweet from dictionary loads and I'm
going to take that string
representation um from of the dictionary
I'm going to load it so it's recognized
within um python as a dictionary and
then I'm going to call the from
dictionary to get the tweet um class so
I'm just adding my tweet object um to
the Tweet attribute within the track
tweet and then I'm getting my track
Tweet back again here I have some
methods I've got two string which is
going to be helpful for uh returning a
string that we can save down uh within
the text file and then I've got some
update um status so when we actually uh
send the status I'll call this function
and I can just update with the new
status and then we can update our gen
status when we've actually generated it
using open
API so at tweet que all I'm doing now is
taking all those track tweets and I'm
just getting a big list so this is going
to be um a way that we can manage our
tweet pipeline for processing generating
and posting so there's been a bit of a
hierarchy we have a tweet then we're
tracking that tweet and now I'm going to
have a huge cue so this data class is
just going to manage that cue so I can
handle all the processing generating and
posting we're going to have some
properties I want a subset of all these
track tweets I want to know which ones
have not been sent which ones have not
been generated and then I want tweets a
list of tweets that are ready for
sending so that haven't been sent and
that are
generated I want a way that I can
actually add new tweets to this list so
onq and then DQ so we've we've got a bit
of a queing methodology for this class I
also want a way that I can then take my
text file and then create track tweets
and there for tweets and then a way that
I can go to the text file and save
everything back
down so in summary this file is just our
data structure and how we're then saving
reading and creating classes so we can
process and use them in an efficient way
within our code so if we look at if I
just process my tweets I'm going to take
a text file which is going to be our raw
data file that we've just come up with
I'm then going to use the Tweet cue I'm
going to from text file pass this text
file and I'm going to get my uh my sets
of objects of my track tweets and then
they're going to have individual tweets
attached to them and then I'm going to
Define my large language model and I
want to be able to generate tweets so
I'm going to pass the generate tweets
function that we have up here I'm going
to um pass the large language model the
Tweet q and then the text file then
within the generate tweets now I'm
iterating through that subsection of my
tweet queue for the property tweets not
generated so I'm running through a list
of the tracked tweets for the tweets
that have not been
generated I'm then generating a response
using my gen response um function before
where I'm just passing attributes of the
Tweet track as the topic and the title I
get those responses back in the short
and long responses this entire part here
is just about ensuring that for each
response for my hook for my intro for my
explanation that it's no longer than 280
characters if if the long response is
less than 280 characters I want to take
that if the short response is less than
280 characters I'll take that if the
short response is longer than that I'm
just going to have to cut it off and the
sentence won't make a lot of sense um
but there's not much I can do here if I
don't if I want to have a hands-off
approach Automation and not have to
worry about it so there's a value issue
with the tweet I want to pass it to the
log so I can understand more so now
we're talking about the Twitter feed bot
so now we've got a tweet type and I'm
getting my thread I've got my uh
directories I'm loading my Twitter API
keys and I've got my uh open API key so
I'm setting up basic login now I have a
class which is going to be a um a class
that helps us organize our code and
manage the shared State across our
entire app so here I'm going to
initialize this class so this class is
going to be a processing class primarily
we're going to initialize it with the
Twitter API the Twitter API we're going
to be using is twey so here I have to
pass the client which is my Bearer key
My Consumer key my API key my API secret
and then my access token and my access
token secret I'm also going to
initialize the large language model
which is going to be my chat open API
again with the parameters that we had
talked about before in our jupyter
notebook I'm initializing my text file
with the function that I had um
initialized at the top of the this
script um and then I'm also initializing
my tweet CU so I'm taking my tweet Q
from text file as I initialize I am
using this initialized text file value
to get my tweet cue in that class
object so I want a few things I want to
be able to process tweets generate the
tweets from here I want to be able to
verify um tweets to send so I want to
make make sure that I actually have a
tweet to send one is ready and one's
ready for sending so here I'm using that
property tweets um ready for sending if
it's equal to zero I need to process
tweets process tweets calls the generate
tweets function as we've just talked
about before and it saves it down to the
text file so post thread is going to be
um when we want to post in thread and
we're going to send our tweet so we've
got our uh tweet and I want a dictionary
to be able to pass it so I'm taking my
structure and then I'm using the data
class as dictionary to get it back to a
dictionary format I'm going to run
through my tweet threads as items so
they're going to be items um in the
dictionary I'm going to get back my key
and I'm going to get back my thread that
I want to send so if the key is the
first one so the hook I want to just
send that as a create the Tweet however
if it's anything after that I want to
then take that latest ID last tweet ID
it's going to be equal to thator tweet
thread and I want to pass that through
this function again uh through this
iterator for Loop to then get the last
ID and the way that I do that I can
subsection that I can take the attribute
data and then I can uh get the key
ID so I'm then going to create the Tweet
text exactly the same but this time I'm
including an extra parameter it called
in reply to tweet id id where I'm just
uh getting the last ID and I'm saving
that down every time I run through this
for Loop um for the last tweet thread
that I've used now to post an individual
tweet all I'm going to do is go tweet to
text use my um my previous function that
I've created to get a tweet to to text
format and then I'm just going to create
my tweet by sending it um with a Twitter
API if it's true then I'm going to make
some logs if there's an exception and I
want to log the warning I'm going to
create one extra function which is going
to be to save the file down so I've got
my tweet queue I'm going back to text
file and I'm going to save it to myself.
text file loging latest version of tweet
save down so running my fee my Twitter
bot so I've got this function and if
this is the main function running I want
to call this function so I'm going to
first step to import uh the Twitter
twiter bot initialize this class which
is going to help me process so ensure
that there are tweets to send so I want
to verify the Tweet to send so I have
this search next tweet function and all
that does is that searches through sorts
a list based on the Tweet ID and it uh
then just takes a sorted list of all the
Tweet cues and then gets the first
element of the tweets not sent um
function once I have my Quant tweet
track then I need to either post as a
single tweet or as a um a thread so this
is just going to be an IFL statement on
the an num type that I created before
which is the Tweet type and so here
before I'd made the settings at the top
of this file equal to thread therefore
we're going to post thread so if
twitter. poost thread and then I give it
that
file then all I'm going to do is go
Quant tweet track. update Cent status
that was a lot of code but I just tried
to run through all the aspects there are
just four components we've got the call
open API we got the process the tweets
we've got the actual Twitter um class
structures which handles the data which
are just data classes a way for us to
Define what the tweets are how to track
them and then to put them into a Quee
that we can then process them with and
then I had my main function which was my
twitterbot my main uh
script so now I need a systematic way to
actually call that entire module which
I've called quore feed so here we're
going to be using the
AP um scheduler from package from Python
and we're going to be using the
scheduler background background
scheduler so this is just a main
function that I'm going to be running
which is on um the highest level of my
application and I want to schedule a
background scheduler with the demon I
want to run once this function so that I
can publish and make sure that um my
Twitter bot has actually been deployed
and then once that runs once and I
actually send a tweet then from then
onwards it's going to add a scheduler
using the scheduler add job for this
function and I've set an interval of
every 12 hours could make this 24 could
make this once a week whatever you
want here I've got the start scheduler
and I'm starting the scheduler and I'm
creating an infinite Loop um and I'm
just going to keep holding this until
it's interrupted so now I'm just on my
Twitter server so this is a Raspberry Pi
setup I won't talk about how I've done
that today um because I've I've put all
the details within my GitHub repository
within the rme file on how to set that
up um but here's uh essentially uh the
processing of all the
tweets as you can see the other thing
that I wanted to mention is that we've
got this status um bot which I can call
and then I can
also stop my Twitter service at any time
and we can check the status and we can
see that the bot has been stopped or we
can start the twitterbot
service so checking the status again we
can see that it's live and going so
through this uh methodology once
deployed you can then use uh the
operating Service uh services to
actually start and stop your Twitter bot
so now that mine's in production um it's
very easy to let it be um and for a
number of days um I'm going to be able
to sit here and be twittering away so
now because I have a server where I have
my twitterbot deployed on my Raspberry
Pi I don't need to worry about content
generation in quantitative Finance for
my Twitter account it's automated I'm
using open API um to get and produce my
Twitter content based off a title and a
topic I'm then being able to use and
process that information to then publish
um this intermittently every 12 hours uh
until I run out of Twitter ideas so
hopefully you got a lot out of this
again on my GitHub I have all the
information about how to deploy this uh
service GitHub repository is going to be
linked into the description of this
video again you could change this to be
any topic you just need to go through
that prompt engineering Jupiter notebook
change up the topic that you're
interested in and pass in different
titles and topics to the actual generate
resp response function to then deploy it
on a server then you can follow these
steps to see the deployment steps and
set up your service now I appreciate
this was a little bit different content
to what I'm usually doing but I did want
to publish um how I've created this
Twitter box because I think it might be
useful for other people so again all the
code is linked on my GitHub thank you
very much for listening and until next
time see you
later
[Music]